[
	{
		"question": "What does Santa suffer from if he gets stuck in a chimney?",
		"answer": "Claus-trophobia!",
		"id": 1,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What happened to the man who stole an Advent Calendar?",
		"answer": "He got 25 days!",
		"id": 2,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "Who delivers presents to baby sharks at Christmas?",
		"answer": "Santa Jaws!",
		"id": 3,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What do they sing at a snowman’s birthday party?",
		"answer": "Freeze a jolly good fellow!",
		"id": 4,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What do Santa’s little helpers learn at school?",
		"answer": "The elf-abet!",
		"id": 5,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What kind of motorbike does Santa ride?",
		"answer": "A Holly Davidson!",
		"id": 6,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What did Santa do when he went speed dating?",
		"answer": "He pulled a cracker!",
		"id": 7,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "Why was the turkey in the pop group?",
		"answer": "Because he was the only one with drumsticks!",
		"id": 8,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What do you get if you cross Santa with a duck?",
		"answer": "A Christmas Quacker!",
		"id": 9,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What goes “Oh, Oh, Oh”?",
		"answer": "Santa walking backwards!",
		"id": 10,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "Why was the snowman looking through the carrots?",
		"answer": "He was picking his nose!",
		"id": 11,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "Why does Santa have three gardens?",
		"answer": "So he can ‘ho ho ho’!",
		"id": 12,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the best Christmas present in the world?",
		"answer": "A broken drum, you just can’t beat it!",
		"id": 13,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What do snowmen wear on their heads?",
		"answer": "Ice caps!",
		"id": 14,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What did Adam say the day before Christmas?",
		"answer": "“It’s Christmas, Eve!”",
		"id": 15,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What do you get when you cross a snowman with a vampire?",
		"answer": "Frostbite!",
		"id": 16,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What did the stamp say to the Christmas card?",
		"answer": "Stick with me and we’ll go places!",
		"id": 17,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "Why did no one bid for Rudolph and Blitzen on eBay?",
		"answer": "Because they were two deer!",
		"id": 18,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What does the Queen call her Christmas Broadcast?",
		"answer": "The One Show!",
		"id": 19,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "Why don’t you ever see Santa in hospital?",
		"answer": "Because he has private elf care!",
		"id": 20,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "How did Mary and Joseph know Jesus’ weight when he was born?",
		"answer": "They had a weigh in a manger!",
		"id": 21,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "Why is it getting harder to buy Advent calendars?",
		"answer": "Their days are numbered!",
		"id": 22,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "How did Scrooge win the football game?",
		"answer": "The ghost of Christmas passed!",
		"id": 23,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What do angry mice send to each other at Christmas?",
		"answer": "Cross-mouse cards!",
		"id": 24,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	},
	{
		"question": "What do you call a bunch of chess players bragging about their games in a hotel lobby?",
		"answer": "Chess nuts boasting in an open foyer!",
		"id": 25,
		"gif": "PUT GIF URL HERE",
		"song": "PUT SONG URL HERE"
	}
]